http://www.dolly.com/privacy

Dolly Privacy PolicyLast Revised: May 22, 2015This Privacy Policy explains how information about you is collected, used and disclosed by Dolly, Inc. ("Dolly"). This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect when you use our website, mobile application and other online products and services (collectively, the "Services") or when you otherwise interact with us.We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make changes, we will notify you by revising the date at the top of the policy and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to our homepage or sending you a notification). We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy whenever you access the Services or otherwise interact with us to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy.Collection of InformationInformation You Provide to UsWe collect information you provide directly to us. For example, we collect information when you create an account, participate in any interactive features of the Services, fill out a form, create a request for loading, unloading, moving, hauling, packing, lifting, assembly or disassembly, pay for services provided to you, apply for a job, communicate with us via third party social media sites, request customer support or otherwise communicate with us. The types of information we may collect include your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, credit card information, information about the items you want loaded, unloaded, moved, hauled, packed, lifted, assembled or disassembled, and any other information you choose to provide.Information We Collect Automatically When You Use the ServiceWhen you access or use our Services, we automatically collect information about you, including:Log Information: We collect log information about your use of the Services, including the type of browser you use, access times, pages viewed, your IP address and the page you visited before navigating to our Services.Device Information: We collect information about the computer or mobile device you use to access our Services, including the hardware model, operating system and version, unique device identifiers and mobile network information.Location Information: We may collect information about the location of your device each time you access or use one of our mobile applications or otherwise consent to the collection of this information. For more details, please see "Your Choices" below.Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: We and our service providers use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory that help us improve our Services and your experience, see which areas and features of our Services are popular, report ad impressions, interactions with ad impressions and ad services, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see "Your Choices" below.Use of InformationWe may use information about you for various purposes, including to:Provide, maintain and improve our Services;Provide, communicate about and deliver the products and services you request, process transactions and send you related information, including confirmations and invoices;Send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages;Respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service;Communicate with you about products, services, and offers offered by Dolly and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;Personalize and improve the Services and provide advertisements, content or features that match user profiles or interests;Link or combine with information we get from others to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; andCarry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.Dolly is based in the United States and the information we collect is governed by U.S. law. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries.Sharing of InformationWe may share information about you as follows or as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:With vendors, consultants and other service providers who need access to such information to carry out work on our behalf;With third parties for their own services and marketing purposes, unless you opt out of this type of sharing by emailing support@dolly.com;In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Dolly or others;In connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing or acquisition of all or a portion of our business by another company;Between and among Dolly and its parent, subsidiaries and affiliated companies; andWith your consent or at your direction.We may also share aggregated or de-identified information, which cannot reasonably be used to identify you.Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by OthersWe use services from Google, Facebook and other third party providers to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of the Services and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information. This information may be used by Dolly and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Services and other websites and better understand your online activity.SecurityDolly takes reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.Your ChoicesAccount InformationYou may update, correct or delete information about you at any time by logging into your online account or emailing us at support@dolly.com. If you wish to delete or deactivate your account, please email us at support@dolly.com or delete our mobile application from your device, but note that we may retain certain information as required by law or for legitimate business purposes. We may also retain cached or archived copies of information about you for a certain period of time.Location InformationWhen you first launch any of our mobile applications that collect location information, you will be asked to consent to the application's collection of this information. We currently require this location information in order to use our Services, so if you do not consent to this collection, you cannot use our Services. If you initially consent to our collection of location information, you can subsequently stop the collection of this information at any time by changing the preferences on your mobile device. If you do so, our mobile applications, or certain features thereof, will no longer function. You may also stop our collection of location information by following the standard uninstall process to remove all of our mobile applications from your device.CookiesMost web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove or reject browser cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.Promotional CommunicationsYou may opt out of receiving promotional mails, push notifications or text messages from Dolly by following the instructions in those communications or by adjusting the settings on your mobile device. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional communications, such as those about your account, products or services you've requested or our ongoing business relations.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@dolly.com.
